Contact

sambitsargam2003@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sambitsargam-ekalabya-5b56251b7 (LinkedIn) sambitsargam.study (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Software Development
Microsoft Azure
Google Cloud Platform (GCP)

Certifications
CockroachDB

Sambit Sargam Ekalabya

Web developer

Kendujhar

Summary

Experienced with a demonstrated history of working in the human resources industry. Skilled in Oracle Database, Project Estimation, IT Infrastructure Management, Big Data Analytics, and IT Service Management. Strong community and social services professional with a Bachelor of Technology - BTech focused in Information Technology from National Institute of Science and Technology (NIST), Berhampur.

Experience

AngelHack Ambassador September 2021 - Present (3 months)

Coding Elements

Ambassador

December 2020 - Present (1 year)

Lyriclious - Learn with us Campus Ambassador March 2021 - April 2021 (2 months)

Collegedunia
Ambassador
December 2020 - February 2021 (3 months)

Education

National Institute of Science and Technology (NIST), Berhampur Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (2020 - 2024)